http://www.hashauctions.com/privacy-policy

HomeServicesContact UsPast AuctionsHomeServicesContact UsPast AuctionsHomeServicesContact UsPast AuctionsMoreHomeServicesContact UsPast AuctionsHomeServicesContact UsPast Auctions
Privacy Notice for Hash Auctions
& auctioneer or auction houseThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for https://www.hashauctions.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you  through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We  only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via  email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this  information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason  you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third  party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill  your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future  to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this  privacy policy.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit  sensitive information via the website, your information is protected  both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data),  that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.  You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and  looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted  online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who  need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or  customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable  information. The computers/servers in which we store personally  identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Registration In order to use this website, a user must first complete the  registration form. During registration a user is required to give  certain information (such as name and email address). This information  is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which  you have expressed interest.Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a  site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and  identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a  cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more  than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also  enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the  experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any  personally identifiable information on our site.Sharing We share aggregated demographic information with our interest-based  advertising. This is not linked to any personal information that can  identify any individual person.
Copyright © 2020 Hash Auctions - All Rights Reserved.License VAAR #2032|Firm #692|WV #1122|PA #AU003641R 540-955-0277 info@hashauctions (dotcom)Privacy Policy
